pandacashback.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy Coupons - Privacy Policy Coupon Codes, Cashback, Deals

## **Collection and Use of Personal Information:**

We collect the following personal information from you:

\- Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

\- Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

\- Preferences Information you provide such as product or content interests, or communication or marketing preferences

\- Usage activity about how you interact with us such as purchase history, what content you viewed, and which areas of our site you visited.

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

**We use this information to:**

\- Fulfill your order

\- Send you an order confirmation

\- Send you requested product or service information

\- Respond to customer service requests

\- Administer your account

\- Send you a newsletter

\- Improve our Web site and marketing efforts

\- Respond to your questions and concerns

\- Display content based upon your interests

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at admin@pandacashback.com.

**Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

## Disclosure to Third Parties

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary to provide_  these services to us.

We may disclose your personal information

\- As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

\- when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

\- If PANDA CASHBACK LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

\- To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

_PayPal_

If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

_Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider_

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose. 

## Tracking Technologies

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within our site and which links or ads they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.

## Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at admin@pandacashback.com

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our third party checkout options to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at admin@pandacashback.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Other Information

 Our Web site includes third party hosted widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide single-purpose services (e.g. sharing of articles, videos, etc.). Personal information, like your email address, may be collected and cookies may be set so the widget can work properly. The information through the widget is subject to the widget provider’s privacy policy

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at admin@pandacashback.com.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Us

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

PANDA CASHBACK LLC

22238 Solomon Blvd # 228

Novi, MI  48375 

United States

Email: admin@pandacashback.com
